{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Connelly",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Joseph_Wambaugh",
    "human_readable": "Michael Connelly was influenced by Joseph Wambaugh.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9823827743530273,
            "question": "What is Joseph Wambaugh known for that influenced Michael Connelly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9250311255455017,
            "question": "Who influenced Michael Connelly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8463542461395264,
            "question": "What connection exists between Michael Connelly and Joseph Wambaugh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8339423537254333,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Michael Connelly and Joseph Wambaugh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7769021987915039,
            "question": "Who is considered a literary influence on Michael Connelly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6882454752922058,
            "question": "Which author had an impact on Michael Connelly's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6627421379089355,
            "question": "Michael Connelly's writing style likely reflects the influence of which author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6545051336288452,
            "question": "Who inspired Michael Connelly as a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.497610479593277,
            "question": "Which author's work did Michael Connelly draw inspiration from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37571418285369873,
            "question": "Name the author who served as a role model for Michael Connelly."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Connelly was influenced by Joseph Wambaugh.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5876_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which author's work did Michael Connelly draw inspiration from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5876_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who inspired Michael Connelly as a writer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5876_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Connelly's writing style likely reflects the influence of which author?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5876_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5876_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information that supports the triple, stating that Michael Connelly discovered the work of Raymond Chandler and was inspired by it to create his iconic Harry Bosch novels. It is also mentioned that Joseph Wambaugh's books have been praised by Connelly, indicating a positive influence on him as an author."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information from the documents supports that Michael Connelly was influenced by Joseph Wambaugh, as evidenced by statements like \"Connelly also lists Joseph Wambaugh as another of his main influences\" and the overall context highlighting Wambaugh's significant impact on contemporary crime writers."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}